[
    {
        "question": "Alice said, \"How clever I am !\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "Alice",
          "1": "very",
          "3": "that",
          "2": "is",
          "5": "said",
          "6": "exclaimed",
          "7": "was",
          "8": "clever",
          "9": "she"
        },
        "answers":[[4,6,3,9,7,1,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Geeta cried, \"My God ! I am lost in the forest.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "forest",
          "1": "that",
          "3": "was",
          "2": "in",
          "5": "Geeta",
          "6": "she",
          "7": "her",
          "8": "and",
          "9": "lost",
          "10": "cried",
          "11": "the",
          "12": "exclaimed",
          "13": "God"
        },
        "answers":[[5,10,8,12,1,6,3,9,2,11,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nandita said to Jagdish, \"Happy birthday !\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "Jagdish",
          "1": "a",
          "3": "Nandita",
          "2": "happy",
          "5": "to",
          "6": "wished",
          "7": "asked",
          "8": "birthday"
        },
        "answers":[[3,6,4,1,2,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "He said, \"Oh, if only I am taller !\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "he were",
          "1": "that",
          "3": "be",
          "2": "he",
          "5": "to",
          "6": "he was",
          "7": "wished",
          "8": "taller",
          "9": "he"
        },
        "answers":[[2,7,1,6,8],[2,7,1,4,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "He said, \"How sad that you did not come !\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "was",
          "1": "not",
          "3": "I",
          "2": "sadly",
          "5": "it",
          "6": "that",
          "7": "come",
          "8": "exclaimed",
          "9": "had",
          "10": "sad",
          "11": "he"
        },
        "answers":[[11,8,2,6,3,9,1,7]]
    },
    {
        "question": "She asked me what I was going to do at the weekend.",
        "words": {
          "4": "me",
          "1": "weekend",
          "3": "you", 
          "5": "going",
          "2": "she",
          "6": "what",
          "7": "the",
          "8": "to",
          "9": "at",
          "10": "are",
          "11": "told",
          "12": "were",
          "13": "do"
        },
        "answers":[[2,11,4,6,10,3,5,8,13,9,7,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Deepa asked me how my journey had been.",
        "words": {
          "4": "me",
          "1": "your",
          "3": "Deepa",
          "2": "been",
          "5": "was",
          "6": "asked",
          "7": "journey",
          "8": "is",
          "9": "has",
          "10": "how"
        },
        "answers":[[3,6,4,10,5,1,7]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Navin asked me what I had been doing when he had seen me.",
        "words": {
          "4": "Navin",
          "1": "saw",
          "3": "me",
          "2": "said",
          "5": "you",
          "6": "what",
          "7": "I",
          "8": "to",
          "9": "you",
          "10": "when",
          "11": "were",
          "12": "seeing",
          "13": "doing",
          "14": "was"
        },
        "answers":[[4,2,8,3,6,11,5,13,10,7,1,9]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Michael asked his friend if he could borrow his friend's car on Sunday.",
        "words": {
          "4": "friend",
          "1": "can",
          "3": "Sunday",
          "2": "your",
          "5": "I",
          "6": "Michael",
          "7": "his",
          "8": "car",
          "9": "asked",
          "10": "borrow",
          "11": "on"
        },
        "answers":[[6,9,7,4,1,5,10,2,8,11,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "She asked me whether I had studied indirect speech before.",
        "words": {
          "4": "you",
          "1": "me",
          "3": "she",
          "2": "indirect",
          "5": "have",
          "6": "before",
          "7": "studied",
          "8": "did",
          "9": "to",
          "10": "speech",
          "11": "said",
          "12": "study",
          "13": "when"
        },
        "answers":[[3,11,9,1,5,4,7,2,10,6],[3,11,9,1,8,4,12,2,10,6]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mother ordered us not to play in front of the window.",
        "words": {
          "4": "front",
          "1": "the",
          "3": "us",
          "2": "mother",
          "5": "in",
          "6": "Don't",
          "7": "of",
          "8": "not",
          "9": "play",
          "10": "told",
          "11": "window",
          "12": "to"
        },
        "answers":[[2,10,3,6,9,5,4,7,1,11]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mr. Gomes requested Arindam to shut the door.",
        "words": {
          "4": "Arindam",
          "1": "said",
          "3": "shut",
          "2": "to",
          "5": "Mr. Gomes",
          "6": "please",
          "7": "door",
          "8": "to",
          "9": "the"
        },
        "answers":[[5,1,2,4,6,3,9,7],[5,1,8,4,6,3,9,7]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Parveen wished that she had a new house.",
        "words": {
          "4": "I",
          "1": "a",
          "3": "oh",
          "2": "Parveen",
          "5": "had",
          "6": "if",
          "7": "have",
          "8": "said",
          "9": "house",
          "10": "been",
          "11": "new"
        },
        "answers":[[2,8,3,6,4,7,1,11,9]]
    },
    {
        "question": "He exclaimed with joy that he had won a prize.",
        "words": {
          "4": "Hurrah!",
          "1": "I",
          "3": "he",
          "2": "won",
          "5": "said",
          "6": "a",
          "7": "have",
          "8": "prize"
        },
        "answers":[[3,5,4,1,7,2,6,8],[3,5,4,1,2,6,8]]
    }
]